Guide to the Doris Duke Photograph Collection, 1870-2006
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Doris Duke, 1913-1998
  - Black and white photos of Doris Duke with friends at a dinner party. Cobina Wright, LA Herald & Express columnist, is present wearing black headpiece, circa 1955 (Box 11, Folder PHDD098)
  - Black and white photographs of Doris Duke spending time with a female friend, 1930-1935 (Box 11, Folder PHDD099)
  - Black and white photographs of Doris Duke, James Cromwell, Walker Inman Sr., and other unidentified companions possibly in Charleston, SC, 1930-1935 (Box 11, Folder PHDD100)
  - Black and white photograph of Doris Duke with unidentified woman and chimpanzee, 1930-1935 (Box 11, Folder PHDD101)
  - Color photograph of Doris Duke and possibly Malcolm Forbes, circa 1980 (Box 11, Folder PHDD102)
  - Black and white photograph of Doris Duke on Chris-craft cruiser with unidentified companions, 1935-1940 (Box 11, Folder PHDD103)
  - Black and white photograph of Doris Duke, standing in profile, looking over chain fence, 1930-1935 (Box 11, Folder PHDD104)
  - Sepia photograph of Doris Duke and James Cromwell shortly after their arrival at Singapore in the Malay archipelago during their world honeymoon tour. Doris Duke and James Cromwell were guests of the Sultan of Johore at the Istana Besar and made a trip from Johore Bahru to Singapore in the Sultan's yacht, 1935 Jun 18 (Box 12, Folder PHDD105)
  - Copy of a Black and white photograph of Doris Duke listening to Duke Ellington play the violin, circa 1955 (Box 12, Folder PHDD106)
  - Copy of Black and white photograph of Doris Duke, Joey Castro, and Big Jay McNeeley at Birdland, circa 1955 (Box 12, Folder PHDD107)
  - Black and white photograph of group of four, standing arm in arm. Miss Duke is at the far left and Jimmy Cromwell is at the far right, circa 1936 (Box 12, Folder PHDD108)
  - Color photographs of Doris Duke at a party, circa 1988 (Box 12, Folder PHDD109)
  - Black and white photographs of Doris Duke and James Cromwell travelling abroad, possibly Germany, circa 1935 (Box 12, Folder PHDD110)
  - Black and white photographs of Doris Duke in a European city. Unidentified man in one photo, circa 1940 (Box 12, Folder PHDD113)
  - Black and white photographs of Doris Duke and James Cromwell touring a city in Europe, circa 1938 (Box 12, Folder PHDD114)
  - Negatives of Doris Duke, James Cromwell, Marian Paschal and others, sitting around a table. One negative is of an unidentifiable location, circa 1938 (Box 12, Folder PHDD115)
  - Color photograph of Miss Duke, wearing a green, Asian-inspired outfit with headdress, circa 1989 (Box 12, Folder PHDD116)
  - Portrait of Doris Duke, at six months, 1913 (Box 12, Folder PHDD117)
  - Print of Doris Duke, with hands resting in lap. Miss Duke is wearing pearl bracelets on her left wrist, 1930-1935 (Box 12, Folder PHDD118)
  - Print of Doris Duke, wearing 1 string of pearls, circa 1930 (Box 12, Folder PHDD119)
  - Various color slides documenting trips taken by Doris Duke and Porfirio Rubirosa, friends, and activities. Several images display views, pets, or scenes at Shangri La, circa 1948 (Box 12, Folder PHDD120)
  - Photos of fur collection, taken during inventorying process by A. Perlman, 2005 (Box 12, Folder PHDD121)
  - Sepia portrait of a young Doris Duke, circa 1918 (Box 12, Folder PHDD122)
  - Color Polaroid 3 of Doris Duke's tiara, 2000 (Box 12, Folder PHDD123)
  - Black and white press photo of Doris Duke and James Cromwell during a stay in Washington DC, 1936 (Box 12, Folder PHDD124)
  - Black and white photograph of Doris Duke and James Cromwell on drive to San Francisco, after flight from Hawaii, 1937 (Box 12, Folder PHDD125)
  - Black and white photograph of Miss Duke, sitting on sequined couch, 1972-1975 (Box 12, Folder PHDD126)
  - Color photograph of Doris Duke and Jim Nabors most likely aboard Miss Duke's private airplane, circa 1988 (Box 12, Folder PHDD127)
  - Color photographs of Miss Duke at party. Guests include Franco Rossellini, circa 1985 (Box 12, Folder PHDD128)
  - Color photographs, Chairman Mao, Doris Duke's dog, at Rough Point, 1988 (Box 12, Folder PHDD129)
  - Photographic images of portrait of Doris Duke. Includes negatives, 2006 (Box 12, Folder PHDD130)
  - Color photograph of Doris Duke shaking hands with President Ronald Reagan, 1986 (Box 12, Folder PHDD131)
  - Black and white photograph of Doris Duke with Walker Inman Sr., 1944 (Box 12, Folder PHDD132)
  - Black and white photographs of Miss Duke's dogs. Includes monogrammed photo album, "DDC", undated (Box 12, Folder PHDD133)
  - Various color and Black and white photographs of Miss Duke's dogs, circa 1988 (Box 12, Folder PHDD134)
  - Black and white photograph of Doris Duke with an unidentified gentleman, circa 1940s (Box 12, Folder PHDD135)
  - Black and white photograph of Doris Duke with unknown man, circa 1930s (Box 13, Folder PHDD136)
  - Photographs and negatives, Doris Duke Travel-Cruise on the Lurline, circa 1930s (Box 13, Folder PHDD137)
  - Black and white photographs, Doris Duke Miscellaneous Travel, circa 1930s, 1950s (Box 13, Folder PHDD138)
  - Black and white photographs of Doris Duke-Hawaii, circa 1930s, 1951 (Box 13, Folder PHDD139)
  - Color prints of Doris Duke Travel-Italy, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 13, Folder PHDD140)
  - Color slides documenting various locations, estates, and trips. Includes trips to India, Ceylon, Lisbon, and Caribbean, Duke Farms, and Hawaii, circa 1950s (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder PHDD141)
  - Color slides documenting various locations, estates, and trips. Includes trips to India, Ceylon, Lisbon, and Caribbean, Duke Farms, and Hawaii, circa 1950s (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder PHDD141)
  - Color slide of Doris Duke with Joe Castro at Duke Farms, circa 1950s (Box 13, Folder PHDD142)
  - Color slides, Doris Duke Travel-Aruba and Puerto Rico, circa 1960s (Box 13, Folder PHDD143)
  - Color slides, Doris Duke Travel-Paris, circa 1960s (Box 13, Folder PHDD144)
  - Color photograph of Doris Duke, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 13, Folder PHDD145)
  - Reproduction of Cupie Singh's photo from wedding of then Prime, Maharaja Kumar Bhawani Singh of Jaipur, 1966 Mar 10 (Box 13, Folder PHDD146)
  - Color slides, Doris Duke Travel-Hawaii Tours, slaughtered animals, 1966 Nov (Box 14, Folder PHDD147)
  - Color slides, Doris Duke Travel-Niagara Falls, Park Commons, 1964 Jul 22 (Box 14, Folder PHDD148)
  - Color slides, Doris Duke Travel-Montreal, 1964 Jul 23 (Box 14, Folder PHDD149)
  - Photographs of Doris Duke at different social gatherings, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 14, Folder PHDD150)
  - Color slides, Doris Duke Travel-Russia, Leningrad, and Finland, 1985 Jul (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder PHDD151)
  - Color slides, Doris Duke Travel-Russia, Leningrad, and Finland, 1985 Jul (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder PHDD151)
  - Color prints, Doris Duke Travel-Asia, Middle East and Paris, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder PHDD152)
  - Color photographs of individuals who had received Christmas gifts from the Doris Duke Foundation, 1993 (Box 14, Folder PHDD153)
  - Color slides, Doris Duke Travel-New York City, undated (Box 14, Folder PHDD154)
  - Color slides, Doris Duke Travel-Tahiti, undated (Box 14, Folder PHDD155)
  - Negatives of Doris Duke, miscellaneous. Includes some travel, undated (Box 14, Folder PHDD156)
  - Photographic inventory of Doris Duke's dresses, undated (Box 14, Folder PHDD157)
  - Color glass mounted slides of Doris Duke's trip to the Middle East, 1938 (Box 15, Folder PHDD158)
  - Color glass mounted slides of Doris Duke's trip to the Middle East. Includes Aleppo, Palmyra, 1938 (1 of 2) (Box 15, Folder PHDD159)
  - Color glass mounted slides of Doris Duke's trip to the Middle East. Includes Aleppo, Palmyra, 1938 (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder PHDD159)
  - Color glass mounted slides of Doris Duke's trip to the Middle East. Includes Chihil Sutan, Syria, 1938 (1 of 2) (Box 15, Folder PHDD160)
  - Color glass mounted slides of Doris Duke's trip to the Middle East. Includes Chihil Sutan, Syria, 1938 (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder PHDD160)
  - Color glass mounted slides of Doris Duke's trip to the Middle East. Includes Damascus, Balbek, and Palmyra, 1938 (1 of 2) (Box 15, Folder PHDD161)
  - Color glass mounted slides of Doris Duke's trip to the Middle East. Includes Damascus, Balbek, and Palmyra, 1938 (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder PHDD161)
  - Color glass mounted slides of Doris Duke's trip to the Middle East. Includes Ramsau[?], Damascus, Persepolis, Isfahan, and Mashid, 1938 (1 of 6) (Box 15, Folder PHDD162)
  - Color glass mounted slides of Doris Duke's trip to the Middle East. Includes Ramsau[?], Damascus, Persepolis, Isfahan, and Mashid, 1938 (2 of 6) (Box 15, Folder PHDD162)
  - Color glass mounted slides of Doris Duke's trip to the Middle East. Includes Ramsau[?], Damascus, Persepolis, Isfahan, and Mashid, 1938 (3 of 6) (Box 15, Folder PHDD162)
  - Color glass mounted slides of Doris Duke's trip to the Middle East. Includes Ramsau[?], Damascus, Persepolis, Isfahan, and Mashid, 1938 (4 of 6) (Box 15, Folder PHDD162)
  - Color glass mounted slides of Doris Duke's trip to the Middle East. Includes Ramsau[?], Damascus, Persepolis, Isfahan, and Mashid, 1938 (5 of 6) (Box 15, Folder PHDD162)
  - Color glass mounted slides of Doris Duke's trip to the Middle East. Includes Ramsau[?], Damascus, Persepolis, Isfahan, and Mashid, 1938 (6 of 6) (Box 15, Folder PHDD162)
  - Color glass mounted slides of Doris Duke's trip to the Middle East. Includes Syria, St. Sophia, Bucharest, 1938 (Box 15, Folder PHDD163)
  - Photographs of a wedding which included Doris Duke as a bridesmaid. Possibly in Romania or Italy during World War II, 1943 Apr 15 (Box 15, Folder PHDD169)
  - Photograph of Doris Duke as a bridesmaid at Mary Grace Curley's wedding. Includes letter sent from George Tsourounis, godson of Doris Duke's friend Marion Davies, circa 1930s (Box 16, Folder PHDD164)
  - Black and white photograph of Middle Eastern architecture-Doris Duke Travel-Middle East, circa 1938 (Box 16, Folder PHDD165)
  - Doris Duke and friends on an outing in Hawaii, circa 1939. Reproduction mounted on foam core. (Box 16, Folder PHDD166)
  - Doris Duke and Maharaja Bhawani Singh of Jaipur at a wedding at City Palace in Jaipur, India, 1966 Mar 17. Reproduction mounted on foam core. (Box 16, Folder PHDD167)
  - A portrait of Doris Duke, circa 1953. Reproduction mounted on foam core. (Box 16, Folder PHDD168)
- Duke Endowment, 1961-1970
  The photographs primarily document events hosted by the Duke Endowment. A majority of the photographs are from an album created for "Miss Doris Duke" by the Duke Endowment which details a luncheon celebrating the Duke Endowment's 40th anniversary.
  - Black and white photographs of board members of The Duke Endowment. Trustees include Paul H. Clyde, Ken Towe, Mary Semans, Ben Few, Tom Perkins, and Marshall Pickens. Photo C includes Daryl Hart, President of Duke, circa 1970 (Box 17, Folder PHDE001)
  - Black and white photographs removed from album created for "Miss Doris Duke" from the Duke Endowment. Photos of luncheon document celebration Duke Endowment's 40th anniversary. Others included in photos are Norman A. Cocke, past President of Duke Power (1960s) and Thomas Perkins, 1964 (Box 18, Folder PHDE002)
  - Trustees Meeting held to honor W.C. Davison upon his retirement as the Dean of the Duke Medical School and to observe the opening of the local Endowment office, 1961 Oct (Box 17, Folder PHDE003)
- Duke Farms, 1897-2004
  The images in this series document the transformation of the Duke Farms estate, including original construction and improvements made to the estate. This series primarily consists of black and white and color photographs that detail exterior shots around the estates (including fountains, statues, lakes, bridges and vistas), work on the estate, interior and exterior shots of the main residence and other buildings on the estate, aerial shots, camels Baby and Princess, who spent their summers at the estate, and various events at Duke Farms. Of particular interest are the tinted photographs of Duke Farms scenes dating from the early 1900s.
  - Black and white photographs of Raritan Gate Fountain, 1910-1920 (Box 19, Folder PHDF249)
  - Black and white photographs of Raritan Gate Fountain, different angle than PHDF249, 1910-1920 (Box 19, Folder PHDF250)
  - Black and white photograph and photo reproduction of surrey with hitched pony, Waiting for Doris, circa 1912 (Box 19, Folder PHDF251)
  - Black and white photograph of four workmen with road grader and water tank carriage pulled by team of two horses at Duke Farms, 1910-1920 (Box 19, Folder PHDF252)
  - Black and white photograph of Southeast view of Coach Barn, 1910-1920 (Box 19, Folder PHDF253)
  - Black and white photograph of scenic view of Mud Lake, small waterfall in foreground, and trees and field in background, 1910-1920 (Box 19, Folder PHDF254)
  - Black and white photograph of possibly Raritan River in the Winter. View may be from Nevius Street Bridge looking East, 1910-1920 (Box 19, Folder PHDF255)
  - Black and white photograph of the exterior of the main residence from the east, 1910-1920 (Box 19, Folder PHDF256)
  - Black and white photograph of the exterior of the main residence from slightly further East than shown in PHDF256, 1910-1920 (Box 19, Folder PHDF257)
  - Black and white photograph and reproduction of exterior of main residence, north view from front lawn and edge of road, circa 1908 (Box 19, Folder PHDF258)
  - Black and white photograph of exterior of main residence, slightly different angle than shown in PHDF258. The words, "OFF THE" are cut into the grass in the foreground, circa 1908 (Box 19, Folder PHDF259)
  - Black and white photograph of double view of main residence, positioned top to bottom. Image is similar to PHDG256, 1910-1920 (Box 19, Folder PHDF260)
  - Black and white photograph of exterior of main residence, from road, with well in right foreground, 1910-1920 (Box 19, Folder PHDF261)
  - Black and white photograph of fountain and Bull Durham statue, 1910-1920 (Box 19, Folder PHDF262)
  - Black and white photograph of Horace Trumbauer's early proposal of a country house for James B. Duke in Somerville, NJ, circa 1910 (Box 19, Folder PHDF263)
  - Aerial photos of Duke Farms, 1942 (Box 19, Folder PHDF264)
  - Selection of aerial photographs of Duke Farms from United Aerial Surveys, 1950 Dec 3 (Box 19, Folder PHDF265)
  - Selection of scenic views of Duke Farms taken by John L. Sharpe III, Curator of Rare Books, Duke University, 1987 (Box 19, Folder PHDF266)
  - Series of color photos removed from red and white photo album. File contains images of exteriors of main residence and Japanese garden by house. Also, includes interiors of the Gardens, 1967-1970 (Box 19, Folder PHDF267)
  - Color photos removed from red and white album. Two shots of water body on Duke Farms. Photos attached to page in album entitled, "Writer Weekend Nov. 1969", 1969 (Box 19, Folder PHDF268)
  - Series of color photos removed from red and white album. Photos show grounds, boat house, and statues covered in snow, 1967-1970 (Box 19, Folder PHDF269)
  - Series of color photos removed from red and white album. Photos show interior views of different rooms of main residence, 1967 (Box 19, Folder PHDF270)
  - Photo of proposed country residence at Duke Farms by Horace Trumbauer, circa 1910 (Box 19, Folder PHDF271)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs of the main residence at Duke Farms, 1 exterior, 3 interior (Winter), undated (Box 19, Folder PHDF272)
  - Two aerial photos of farm buildings located on the Ohlgart Farm, undated (Box 19, Folder PHDF273)
  - Black and white photographs of bodies of water and property at Duke Farms. Two shots show a woman (not Doris Duke) in the center of the scene, 1939 (Box 19, Folder PHDF274)
  - Black and white photographs of prayer services held at the site of the old Foundation on Duke Farms. Services were arranged possibly for Easter celebration, 1955-1958 (Box 19, Folder PHDF275)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs that document construction and improvements made to main residence at Duke Farms. Photos show existence of octagonal rooms on either side of the house and after when these structures were removed. Also shown is the deconstruction of the Fountain Terraces and construction of the Box Garden. Includes negatives, 1938 (1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder PHDF276)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs that document construction and improvements made to main residence at Duke Farms. Photos show existence of octagonal rooms on either side of the house and after when these structures were removed. Also shown is the deconstruction of the Fountain Terraces and construction of the Box Garden. Includes negatives, 1938 (2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder PHDF276)
  - Color photographs of Baby and Princess, shortly after their arrival at Duke Farms. Includes negatives, 1988 (Box 20, Folder PHDF277)
  - Rendering of JB Duke's country house proposed by Trumbauer. Poor quality image. Deem inadequate for reproduction, undated (Box 20, Folder PHDF278)
  - Black and white photographs of main residence (club house), fountains, and grounds at Duke Farms, 1907-1910 (Box 20, Folder PHDF279)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs of various vistas at Duke Farms, undated (Box 20, Folder PHDF283)
  - Color photos of vistas throughout Duke Farms, undated (Box 20, Folder PHDF284)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs of vistas around Duke Farms, undated (Box 20, Folder PHDF285)
  - Several black and white photos taken of piano moved from Doris Duke's apartment in Paris to Somerville, NJ, 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder PHDF286)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs showing Doris Duke and guests gathering at main residence of Duke Farms. Rooms include Crystal Room and Pine Room. Guests include Mary Crane and Aleta MacDonald, 1940-1945 (Box 20, Folder PHDF287)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs documenting the uprooting of a large tree on front lawn of main residence. Tree was located near fountains. James B. Duke can be seen wearing white pants and white cap, 1910-1915 (Box 20, Folder PHDF288)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs documenting various scenes at Duke Farms. Photos include the bridge at the Japanese Garden and the Coach Barn, undated (Box 20, Folder PHDF289)
  - Color photos of residence cars and/or vehicles, 1996 (Box 20, Folder PHDF290)
  - Selection of polaroids of various silver items located in Doris Duke's silver closet, undated (Box 20, Folder PHDF291)
  - Reproductions of Black and white photographs showing various fountains and vistas at Duke Farms. First photo in set is of the Mermaid Fountain, 1910-1920 (Box 20, Folder PHDF292)
  - Black and white photographs of jersey cows in and around the Farm Barn, 1950-1955 (Box 20, Folder PHDF293)
  - Negatives of Japanese Garden, near main residence, and flowers on property, undated (Box 20, Folder PHDF294)
  - Aerial photos of Duke Farms. Photos taken using ASA 1600 color film by Betty Bird, 2000 (Box 20, Folder PHDF295)
  - Color photographs documenting effects of Hurricane Floyd on Duke Farms, 1999 (Box 20, Folder PHDF296)
  - Black and white photographs made from glass plate negatives of Duke Farms. Photos include shots of the Orchid Range, Mermaid Pool, sculptures, and fountains, 1910-1920 (Box 20, Folder PHDF297)
  - Black and white photographs of a variety of structures on Duke Farms. Structures include the main residence, the new Greenhouses, and possibly the interior of the potting shed, circa 1915 (Box 21, Folder PHDF280)
  - Sepia photograph of Pump House, 1907-1910 (Box 21, Folder PHDF281)
  - Aerial View of main residence and surrounding land of Duke Farms, 1999 (Box 21, Folder PHDF282)
  - Color photographs of storm damage to the main residence. Photos by Cupie Singh, 1995 (Box 22, Folder PHDF298)
  - Color photographs of staff room, kitchen and butler's pantry of main residence, circa 1990 (Box 22, Folder PHDF299)
  - Color photographs of Dining Room, main residence, Duke Farms, circa 1990 (Box 22, Folder PHDF300)
  - Color photographs of Palm Room in main residence, Duke Farms, circa 1990 (Box 22, Folder PHDF301)
  - Color photographs of Crystal Room, main residence, Duke Farms, circa 1990 (Box 22, Folder PHDF302)
  - Color photographs of Yellow Room, main residence, Duke Farms, circa 1990 (Box 22, Folder PHDF303)
  - Color photographs of Library, Flower Room, and former office of Doris Duke's, circa 1990 (Box 22, Folder PHDF304)
  - Color photographs of Carport, Main Entrance, Mens Room and Ladies Room of main residence, Duke Farms, circa 1990 (Box 22, Folder PHDF305)
  - Selection of color photographs of vistas at Duke Farms, 2004 (Box 22, Folder PHDF306)
  - Selection of color photographs of some objects sold at auction from the main residence. Includes one transparency of Redon painting, Vase au guerrier Japonais, circa 1905, 2004 (Box 22, Folder PHDF307)
  - Color photograph of Princess, camel, and one of the mini ponies at Duke Farms, 2001 (Box 22, Folder PHDF309)
  - Color Polaroids of interior light fixtures at House 49A, circa 1985 (Box 22, Folder PHDF310)
  - Color photographs of tents and staff at Poetry Festival at Duke Farms, 2004 Sep (Box 22, Folder PHDF311)
  - Black and white photographs of Doris Duke's swimming pool and the Pine Room, at the main residence, Duke Farms, 1937 (Box 22, Folder PHDF312)
  - Photo reproduction of rendering of proposed Country House for James B. Duke, designed by Horace Trumbauer. Photo is a reproduction of original painting, circa 1910, undated (Box 22, Folder PHDF313)
  - Photo reproductions created from scanned postcards. Photos are of conservatory or original greenhouse, circa 1910 (Box 22, Folder PHDF315)
  - Black and white photographs and color photographs of scenes, boulder-style walls, and entrances at Duke Farms. Photos prepared during research for National Register of Historic Places nomination, 1985 (Box 22, Folder PHDF316)
  - Color photographs of cars and/or vehicles at Duke Farms. Photos originally part of automobile inventory, August, 1996. (Box 22, Folder PHDF319)
  - Color photographs of lawn outside of main residence. One photo depicts Doris Duke's camels, Baby and Princess, 1988 (Box 22, Folder PHDF321)
  - Color photographs of the Visitor Center and surrounding areas of the interior gardens, circa 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder PHDF318)
  - Color photographs of Baby and Princess at Coach Barn, Duke Farms, 1988 (Box 24, Folder PHDF323)
  - Color photographs of deer at Duke Farms, undated (Box 24, Folder PHDF324)
  - Color photographs depicting various scenes at Duke Farms. Includes images of main residence, Japanese garden, Farnese bull, dogs, and sheep, 1947-1953 (Box 24, Folder PHDF325)
  - Black and white photograph of River Bridge or Nevius Street Bridge. Power House and Filter House shown in background, 1912 Dec (Box 24, Folder PHDF326)
  - Black and white mounted photographs of Duke Farms, 1897 (Box 25, Folder PHDF327)
  - Sepia photographs of Duke Farms operations, circa late 1800s - early 1900s (Box 24, Folder PHDF328)
  - Photographs and negatives of Duke Farms (includes Doris Duke's pets), 1940s-1960s (Box 24, Folder PHDF329)
  - Photographs of buildings in New Jersey, presumably related to improvements to Duke Island County Park, 1964 Nov 16 (Box 24, Folder PHDF330)
  - Photographs of furniture to be repaired and upholstered at Duke Farms, circa 1970s (Box 24, Folder PHDF331)
  - Photograph inventory of repairs to interior fountain at Duke Farms and tree damage to Main Residence, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 24, Folder PHDF332)
  - Snapshots of flooded areas at Duke Farms, 1978 Jan 26 (Box 24, Folder PHDF333)
  - Color photographs of new milk parlor and silo at Duke Farms, 1980 Jan (Box 24, Folder PHDF334)